Hey, my name is Kibet. I'm one of the founders at Collie and Shoulder to Shoulder brings me basically two things
Primarily one is perspective. I love that there's different entrepreneurs from different backgrounds and different businesses
and they they we really try to challenge each other and
This perspective often helped me grow and also secondly in that aspect is like through the guided sessions at times
You will be prompted with different questions that might
Take you a bit in an uncomfortable zone or in a zone where you really have to think bigger
And I love that aspect because sometimes you are just limiting yourself for no good reason and that second aspect is the also the
Accountability which I really appreciate because I'm not sure about you guys
but if I commit to something I up hold myself to it much better and
Yeah, sometimes a bit uncomfortable, but this is a big nice way to grow